# SEBASTIAN CURTIS LAVARIAS

**WEB DEVELOPER** 

Mobile: 09972217704

E-mail: sebastiancurtislavarias@gmail.com

Web: https://bastilavarias.github.io Github: https://github.com/bastilavarias

Home Address:

406 Sta Fe St. Tondo Manila, Philippines

## **SUMMARY**

I'm Sebastian Curtis Lavarias, 22 years old. I believe that great things can be done by a group of people through unity, trust, and teamwork. I make sure to follow through and finish the commitments that I have and I can adapt easily to different kinds of situations.

# **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

- HTML, CSS and JavaScript
- Vue.js / Sass
- PHP / Laravel / Node.js
- SOL
- Amazon Web Services
- Git

# **EDUCATION**

#### Universidad De Manila

BS Information Technology 2018 - Present

# Metropolitan Medical Center College of Arts Science & Technology

Senior Highschool 2016 - 2018

## **Tondo High School**

Highschool 2012 - 2016

# Magat Salamat Elementary School

Elementary 2006 - 2012

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## **Outsourced Front-end Developer**

<u>Vaskeappen</u> | Drøbak, Norway Nov 2020 - Present

#### **Outsourced Front-end Developer**

<u>GNX</u> | Amsterdam, Netherlands Feb 2020 – Dec 2020

#### Web Developer

<u>Fourello</u> | Philippines Dec 2019 - Present

# **WORK PROJECTS**

#### Medgate

Medgate is the leading international provider of telemedicine, with operations in Switzerland, the Middle East, Australia, India and the Philippines.

- Role: Web Developer
- Techonologies: PHP/Laravel, JavaScript/Vuejs, AWS

### **Inspire Church**

Inspire App is designed to publish content and have the church members watch or listen to these contents.

- Role: Web Developer
- Techonologies: PHP/Laravel, JavaScript/Vuejs, AWS

#### **Z-WELL**

Z-Well Philippine Realty Development Corp is a Philippine-based realestate corporation.

- Role: Web Developer
- Techonologies: PHP/Laravel, JavaScript/Vuejs, AWS

### Vaskeappen

A mobile app that connects customers to self-employed cleaners with just a few taps of their fingers.

- Role: Front-end Developer
- Techonologies: JavaScript/Vuejs, AWS

#### **GNX Customer Management Dashboard**

GNX dashboard for tracking client's installations and managing products and customers.

- Role: Front-end Developer
- Techonologies: JavaScript/Vuejs, AWS